norvax.com 2007-12-25

# Insurance Technology from Norvax

### Privacy Policy 

At Norvax we care about your privacy and want you to feel comfortable and secure in your use of our site. We urge you to read this notice explaining our online information practices. By visiting Norvax at www.norvax.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice. This site is optimized for usage in browsers that comply with W3C standards. It has been modified so that it also works in Internet Explorer 6+.

#### There are two types of information that we collect:

  1. **Personal Information** \- this is "individually identifiable" information you provide to us. 
  2. **Aggregate Information** \- Standard web server/visitor traffic information, regarding overall website traffic patterns. Normally, web servers collect this type of basic information as part of their web log processes. We do not report on individual user sessions. 

#### How is this information used?

**Personal Information**

For certain transactions, Norvax requests individually identifiable information from its users. For example, information requests, contributions, etc. This information may include the following:

First and last name, street address, city, state, zip code, telephone number, email address, and subject of inquiry (i.e., information requests).

**Aggregate Information**

In addition to information provided by our users, Norvax uses the normal Internet tracking tools associated with standard Internet protocols and web-based systems. This system information is typically stored in log files and is used for aggregate reporting. Aggregate reporting includes: total number of visitors, most visited sections, peak traffic times, etc. 

Log files are simply transaction records that web servers maintain. These log files are used for recording information, such as: service provider IP addresses, browser versions, referring websites, search terms used, average number of pages requested, average duration of visit, and/or total visitor traffic.

We use aggregate information gathered from your visit to better design our website. This information supplies us with a broad picture of how people use our website and helps us to manage our system and better serve our users. 

#### Important Information Regarding Links to Other Sites

This Norvax website contains links to other websites that are not under its control. Norvax is not responsible for the content of any linked website, or any link contained in a linked website, or any changes or updates to such websites. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Norvax of that website.

Norvax reserves the right to change this policy at any time. At all times, our privacy policy will be kept up-to-date and clearly posted on our website.

Questions about our privacy policy? Please Contact Us.
